{
  "sections": [
    {
      "title": "Rules",
      "chats": [
        {
          "indexTitle": "Rules",
          "question": "## Rules",
          "answer": "### 1. Drink 3 glasses of water daily !  \n### 2. Max 1 of each: coffe, tea, milk, syroup with water daily !  \n---\n### 3. No more screen time that 2hrs, other than coding or tutorials !  \n---\n### 4. Start coding by 7 !  \n### 5. Code for 3 hrs, 6 pomodoro daily; 2 hrs, 4 pom. on weekends !  \n**(Docs add some time to it, but it should be no more that 15 min spent on these small notes docs so i dont count it.)**\n### 6. Tutorials for 1hr, 2 pomodoro daily !  \n---\n### 7. No coding past 18:00 !  \n### 8. No computers past 20:00 !  \n### 9. No mobile phone past 22:00 !\n---\n### 10. Sleep 8 hrs, from 23:00 most late !  \n### 11. Note fall aslep time daily ! (from last night sleep)\n---\n### 12. Exercice daily !  \n### 13. Walk at least weekly !",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-09T13:03:38.593Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "Template",
          "question": "Template",
          "answer": "```markdown\n| Rule     | Result  | Note             |\n|:----------|:----------:|-----------------:|\n| 1.         | 0           |                     |\n| 2.         | 0           |                     |\n| 3.         | 0           |                     |\n| 4.         | 0           |                     |\n| 5.         | 0           | 6 pomodoro |\n| 6.         | 0           | 2 pomodoro |\n| 7.         | 0           |                     |\n| 8.         | 0           |                     |\n| 9.         | 0           |                     |\n| 10.       | 0           |                     |\n| 11.       | 0           |  23:00          |\n| 12.       | 0           |                     |\n| 13.       | 0           |                     |\n```\n",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-09T13:01:26.651Z"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Log",
      "chats": [
        {
          "indexTitle": "01.01.2024",
          "question": "01.01.2024",
          "answer": "| Rule     | Result  | Note     |\n| :---------|:----------:|----------:|\n| 1.  | 1|  |\n| 2.  | 1 |  |\n| 3.  | 0 |  |\n| 4.  | 0|  |\n| 5.  | 1 | 8 pomodoro |\n| 6.  | 1 | 2 pomodoro |\n| 7.  | 0|  |\n| 8.  | 0 |  |\n| 9.  | 0 |  |\n| 10.  | 0|  |\n| 11.  | 0 |  |\n| 12.  | 0 |  |",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-02T22:12:47.482Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "02.01.2024",
          "question": "02.01.2024",
          "answer": "| Rule     | Result  | Note             |\n|:----------|:----------:|-----------------:|\n| 1.         | 1           |                     |\n| 2.         | 0           | Syroup end  |\n| 3.         | 0           |                     |\n| 4.         | 0           |                     |\n| 5.         | 1           | 11 pomodoro |\n| 6.         | 1           | 2 pomodoro |\n| 7.         | 0           |                     |\n| 8.         | 0           |                     |\n| 9.         | 0           |                     |\n| 10.       | 0           |                     |\n| 11.       | 0           |                     |\n| 12.       | 0           |                     |",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-02T22:19:02.946Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "03.01.2024",
          "question": "03.01.2024",
          "answer": "| Rule     | Result  | Note             |\n|:----------|:----------:|-----------------:|\n| 1.         | 0           |                     |\n| 2.         | 0           |                     |\n| 3.         | 0           |                     |\n| 4.         | 0           |                     |\n| 5.         | 1           | 10 pomodoro |\n| 6.         | 1           | 2 pomodoro |\n| 7.         | 0           |                     |\n| 8.         | 0           |                     |\n| 9.         | 0           |                     |\n| 10.       | 0           |                     |\n| 11.       | 0           |                     |\n| 12.       | 0           |                     |\n",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-03T22:59:01.472Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "04.01.2024",
          "question": "04.01.2024",
          "answer": "| Rule     | Result  | Note             |\n|:----------|:----------:|-----------------:|\n| 1.         | 1           |                     |\n| 2.         | 1           |                     |\n| 3.         | 0           |                     |\n| 4.         | 0           |                     |\n| 5.         | 1           | 8 pomodoro |\n| 6.         | 1           | 2.5 pomodoro |\n| 7.         | 0           |                     |\n| 8.         | 1           |                     |\n| 9.         | 1           |                     |\n| 10.       | 1           |   sleepless last night   |\n| 11.       | 0           |                     |\n| 12.       | 0           |                     |\n",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-04T18:41:00.144Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "05.01.2024",
          "question": "05.01.2024",
          "answer": "| Rule     | Result  | Note             |\n|:----------|:----------:|-----------------:|\n| 1.         | 1           |                     |\n| 2.         | 0           |                     |\n| 3.         | 0           |                     |\n| 4.         | 0           |                     |\n| 5.         | 1           | 8 pomodoro |\n| 6.         | 1           | 2 pomodoro |\n| 7.         | 0           |                     |\n| 8.         | 0           |                     |\n| 9.         | 0           |                     |\n| 10.       | 0           |                     |\n| 11.       | 0           |                     |\n| 12.       | 1           | biedronka    |\n",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-05T23:54:26.381Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "06.01.2024",
          "question": "06.01.2024",
          "answer": "| Rule     | Result  | Note             |\n|:----------|:----------:|-----------------:|\n| 1.         | 0           |                     |\n| 2.         | 0           |                     |\n| 3.         | 0           |                     |\n| 4.         | 0           |                     |\n| 5.         | 0           | 4 pomodoro |\n| 6.         | 1           | 2 pomodoro |\n| 7.         | 0           |                     |\n| 8.         | 0           |                     |\n| 9.         | 0           |                     |\n| 10.       | 0           |                     |\n| 11.       | 0           |                     |\n| 12.       | 0           |                     |\n",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-06T23:07:25.748Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "07.01.2024",
          "question": "07.01.2024",
          "answer": "| Rule     | Result  | Note             |\n|:----------|:----------:|-----------------:|\n| 1.         | 0           |                     |\n| 2.         | 1           |                     |\n| 3.         | 0           |                     |\n| 4.         | 0           |                     |\n| 5.         | 1           | 2,5 pomodoro |\n| 6.         | 1           | 3,5 pomodoro |\n| 7.         | 0           |                     |\n| 8.         | 0           |                     |\n| 9.         | 0           |                     |\n| 10.       | 0           |                     |\n| 11.       | 0           |                     |\n| 12.       | 0           |                     |\n",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-07T21:54:32.985Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "08.01.2024",
          "question": "08.01.2024",
          "answer": "| Rule     | Result  | Note             |\n|:----------|:----------:|-----------------:|\n| 1.         | 0           |                     |\n| 2.         | 1           |                     |\n| 3.         | 0           |                     |\n| 4.         | 0           |                     |\n| 5.         | 1           | 6 pomodoro |\n| 6.         | 1           | 2 pomodoro |\n| 7.         | 0           |                     |\n| 8.         | 0           |                     |\n| 9.         | 0           |                     |\n| 10.       | 0           |                     |\n| 11.       | 0           |                     |\n| 12.       | 0           |                     |\n",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-08T21:49:08.693Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "09.01.2024",
          "question": "09.01.2024",
          "answer": "| Rule     | Result  | Note             |\n|:----------|:----------:|-----------------:|\n| 1.         | 0           |                     |\n| 2.         | 0           |                     |\n| 3.         | 0           |                     |\n| 4.         | 0           |                     |\n| 5.         | 0           | 0 pomodoro |\n| 6.         | 1           | 2 pomodoro |\n| 7.         | 0           |                     |\n| 8.         | 0           |                     |\n| 9.         | 0           |                     |\n| 10.       | 0           |                     |\n| 11.       | 0           |   02:00         |\n| 12.       | 0           |                     |\n| 13.       | 0           |                     |",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-09T13:03:12.294Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "10.01.2024",
          "question": "10.01.2024",
          "answer": "| Rule     | Result  | Note             |\n|:----------|:----------:|-----------------:|\n| 1.         | 1           |                     |\n| 2.         | 1           |                     |\n| 3.         | 0           |                     |\n| 4.         | 0           |                     |\n| 5.         | 1           | 6 pomodoro |\n| 6.         | 1           | 2 pomodoro |\n| 7.         | 1           |                     |\n| 8.         | 0           |                     |\n| 9.         | 0           |                     |\n| 10.       | 0           |                     |\n| 11.       | 0           |  01:00          |\n| 12.       | 1           |  lifting water container                   |\n| 13.       | 0           |                     |\n",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-10T17:09:00.494Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "11.01.2024",
          "question": "11.01.2024",
          "answer": "| Rule     | Result  | Note             |\n|:----------|:----------:|-----------------:|\n| 1.         | 1           |                     |\n| 2.         | 1           |                     |\n| 3.         | 0           |                     |\n| 4.         | 0           |                     |\n| 5.         | 1           | 6 pomodoro |\n| 6.         | 1           | 2 pomodoro |\n| 7.         | 0           |                     |\n| 8.         | 0           |                     |\n| 9.         | 0           |                     |\n| 10.       | 0           |                     |\n| 11.       | 0           |  00:30          |\n| 12.       | 1           | lift water container                    |\n| 13.       | 0           |                     |\n",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-11T20:21:12.571Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "12.01.2024",
          "question": "12.01.2024",
          "answer": "| Rule     | Result  | Note             |\n|:----------|:----------:|-----------------:|\n| 1.         | 0           |                     |\n| 2.         | 1           |                     |\n| 3.         | 0           |                     |\n| 4.         | 0           |                     |\n| 5.         | 1           | 6 pomodoro |\n| 6.         | 1           | 2 pomodoro |\n| 7.         | 0           |                     |\n| 8.         | 0           |                     |\n| 9.         | 0           |                     |\n| 10.       | 0           |                     |\n| 11.       | 0           |  01:00          |\n| 12.       | 0           |                     |\n| 13.       | 0           |                     |\n",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-12T21:55:23.972Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "13.01.2024",
          "question": "13.01.2024",
          "answer": "| Rule     | Result  | Note             |\n|:----------|:----------:|-----------------:|\n| 1.         | 1           |                     |\n| 2.         | 1           |                     |\n| 3.         | 0           |                     |\n| 4.         | 0           |                     |\n| 5.         | 1           | 6 pomodoro |\n| 6.         | 1           | 2 pomodoro |\n| 7.         | 0           |                     |\n| 8.         | 0           |                     |\n| 9.         | 0           |                     |\n| 10.       | 0           |                     |\n| 11.       | 0           |  01:00          |\n| 12.       | 0           |                     |\n| 13.       | 0           |                     |\n",
          "dateTime": "2024-01-13T21:30:06.861Z"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}